Explanation of Database Structure, a high level overview

Before I explain the structure, note that I don't know much about database terminology,
so if I say something that contradicts another thing, it probably means I am using a term as word.
Or the documentaion is shit.


There are fundamental objects that are tracked using a database:
	01. Galleries
	02. Tags
	03. ResourceFiles
	04. SourceInfo
	05. SourceGroups

There are also objects which are used to differentiate or group together fundamental objects of the same type:
	06. Collections
	07. TagTypes
	08. GalleryTypes
	09. TagGroups

There are also types of relations that are tracked in tables
	10. GalleryTags
	11. Favorites
	12. Aliases
	13. Relations


01. Galleries:
	Galleries are a collection of media (different from 3.ResourceFiles and 4.Collections).
	Each Gallery contains descriptive info, a ResourceFile, and Tags.
	The ResourceFile contains the files for the media contained in the Gallery.

02. Tags:
	Tags are tags that are added to describe galleries to make them esier to find.
	Each Tag contains descriptive info, a TagType, and a nullable ResourceFile.
	The ResourceFile in intented to contain a profile image for artists or an example image for trope tags.

03. ResourceFiles:
	ResourceFiles are paths to resources stored in a file systems (outside of the database).
	Each RsourceFile contains a relative file path, a hash, and SourceInfo.
	The hash is used to make sure a resource hasn't been tampered with.

04. SourceInfo:
	SourceInfo contains information about sources that were used to create ResourceFiles.
	Each SourceInfo contains (unix) timestamps, Url to source, CustomInfo, PosterSourceGroups, and a HostSourceGroup.
	The HostSourceGroup corresponds to the host of the content, the website it was found on.
	The HostSourceGroup determines what parser is used (supplied by program implementation) for CustomInfo.
	The PosterSourceGroup can be considered the secondary source group. E.g. a user on Reddit that posts a lot of specific content.
	The CreatorSourceGroup is the source group of the creator, i.e. the artist or dank memer.
	Unlike with tags, you can only have one CreatorSourceGroup, this makes it a bit weird for collabs but you aren't intended to
	have a CreatorSourceGroup for every piece of media in the database. I recommend putting creator social links in the description.
	
05. SourceGroups:
	SourceGroups contain info about a poster or host of sources (resource files).
	Each SourceGroup has a name, url, description and an associated tag.
	The associated tag is to link a source group to an artist.
	The big charcter limit for the description is for social links.


06. Collections:
	Collections are a collection of Galleries.
	Collections are similar to GalleryTags, but contains additional info not related to GalleryTags.

07. TagTypes:
	TagTypes are fundamental types of tags.
	They are used with TagGroups to restrict what tags can be placed in which group.
	e.g. Say you had an Artist type and General type, 
		and say you had a Primary Artist group, a Supporting Artist group, and a General group.
		A tag of type Artist can be tagged under the Primary Artist or Supporting Artists groups but not the General Group.
	See TagGroups for more explanation on why this even exists.

08. GalleryTypes:
	GalleryTypes are fundamental types of galleries.
	This mostly exists for compatability across database implementations. (For future proofing)
	Examples: Comic, Album, Image, Gif, Video, Swf, Document
	May consider doing a Image.png naming scheme (other examples Comic.ltr, Comic.ttb, Document.txt, Document.word)

09. TagGroups:
	TagGrpips are groups of tags of a certain TagType.
	Groups can be used to differentiate primary and secondary groups, but force them to be used only in certain Groups of a type.
	This is so that you could have tags that are specific and tags that are general.
	So that when you are trying to find images related to "bees", you differentiate between images of bees or images related to bees.
	There are more specific use cases but they are dependent on the implemetaion of the program.

10. GalleryTags:
	GalleryTags are used to "tag" galleries.
	GalleryTags contain the gallery to be tagged, the tag to use, and what group to tag them under.

11. Favorites:
	Favorites are used to track favorites of Galleries and Tags.
	The current system is for a single user, since users aren't considered.

12. Aliases:
	Aliases are used to track aliases of Galleries and Tags.
	This could be used to track alternate names of comics or alternate names of artists.
	The names attached directly to Galleries and Tags are considered the primary names.

13. Relations:
	TagRelations are use to track related tags.
	This can be used for recommendation purposes.
	Situations include suggested tags when tagging a gallery, or other tags to browse when browsing by tags,
	or when one gallery has another gallery that is in a differnt format or in color.
